[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Northern Short-tailed Shrew is a small venomous mammal that populates this area.", "correct_answer": "North America", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "Central America and the northern parts of South America", "North and Northeast Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alligators and crocodiles exist together in only one place in the world, where?", "correct_answer": "Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Samoa", "North Carolina", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the doctor orders an EKG, what part of the body is going to be examined?", "correct_answer": "Heart", "incorrect_answers": ["Brain", "Peripheral Nerves", "Abdomen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed The Battleship Potemkin, one of the first great political movies?", "correct_answer": "Sergei Eisenstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrej Munk", "Andrei Tarkovsky", "Stefano Murkovsky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which Asian country is the Giant Panda native?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "India", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played the role of Paul Rayburn, Johns old CIA sidekick, in the 2004 action movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "Christopher Walken", "incorrect_answers": ["Mickey Rourke", "Giancarlo Giannini", "Mario Zaragoza"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is an actual medical term for the fear of peanut butter sticking to the roof of ones mouth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Cagneys last film was the 1961 Billy Wilder satire One, Two, Three.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the occupation of Steve Martins character in the comedy film Planes, Trains  Automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Director of sales", "incorrect_answers": ["Advertising executive", "Attorney", "Doctor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks can only be found in salt water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is the leading producer of apples in the world?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["United states", "France", "Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the body is the cosmetic procedure known as corneal tattooing done?", "correct_answer": "Eyeball", "incorrect_answers": ["Inside of the lower lip", "Genitals", "Tongue"]}]